[{"answer": "All right, what's your husband's first name", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Water and my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What'd you expect? That's his job", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I think I got something", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " What's that, pal", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh? What do you do to make ends meet", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Tell me, how many people a week do you foreclose on", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Neither do I", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " my friend, go to the little girl's room for a minute", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "But, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yes, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, no", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Never", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " So let's just drop the whole thing. Sugar?  Lemon", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Yes, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You may if you can, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I have a cold I can't seem to shake but other than that, I'm fine", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yeah, they are", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You and your husband never discussed her", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "A complete surprise", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "A private investigator", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yeah, got dead drunk, passed out in the bottom of the riverbed", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " Yeah, under that place, what's wrong with that", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What about the water", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "When it comes? What'd you tell him", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "When it comes", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Comes in different parts of the river. Every night a different part", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It wasn't much of a lie", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "But he wasn't killed", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Been meaning to talk to you about that", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " More like other people putting their business in my nose", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Along with Mr. my friend", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Yes. Yes, they were partners", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I never was", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Neither do I, actually. But you hired me or you hired that chippie to hire me", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Never forgave him for what", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "For talking him into building it, he never forgave my father... They haven't spoken to this day", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Of course I'm sure", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "She ain't exactly long in the tooth now", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You must be thinking of a different daughter", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You must be thinking of a different daughter", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "She ran away", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "None", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Too bad", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " 'Course I'm respectable. I'm old. Politicians, ugly buildings and whores all get respectable if they last long enough. I'll double whatever your fees are and I'll pay you ten thousand dollars if you can find my friend' girlfriend", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Yes, his girlfriend", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Maybe", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "You didn't see my friend much, did you", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "If you want to hire me, I still have to know what you and my friend were arguing about", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "How did you find out", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": " You're looking at the owners of a 50,000 acre empire", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "They may not know it but they are", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": " Where did you get this material", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "The apple core", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": " I gave everybody the night off", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "No question from you is innocent, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " There's something black in the green part of your eye", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "...A flaw..", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": " Oh that... It's a flaw in the iris..", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": " ...Yes, sort of a birthmark..", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "It has to do with my father", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "He owns it. You know", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "He owns it. You know", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": " You saw my fa... father? When", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "What did he say?  What did he say", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Do? To who", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "The police", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "She's not tied up", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "What does it look like", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Didn't you call", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "I don't", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "I don't think about it one way or the other. But if you want, give me a day or two, and I'll get back to you. Now I'd like to go home", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "What pictures", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Absolutely", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Yeah, I once knew a whore who for enough money would piss in a customer's face, but she'd never shit on his chest. That's where she drew the line", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "You've got her? Where", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "Two hours... tell me, will my friend be there as well", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "What are you talking about", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Upstairs. Why", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "...she's having a bath now... why do you want to see her", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "I don't know. I mean yes, probably", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "What are you saying", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "That's good. Now what's her name", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "my friend?... my friend who", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "Right now, Curly. It can't wait", "docId": "Chinatown.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": " Tell her later", "qsentId": 92}]